searchengage.com 2016-04-28

# PRIVACY POLICY

                       PRIVACY POLICY
         Thank        you      for      visiting       Cro-bit      Ltd.
  (http://www.searchengage.com/) together with all content on the
  site including sub-domains and other websites operated by Cro-bit
  Ltd. or its affiliates (“Cro-bit Ltd.” and the “Site” respectively).
  Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we
  provide this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) explaining our online
  information practices about the way your information is collected
  and used at this Site. This Privacy Policy applies also to information
  that Cro-bit Ltd. collects and receives from visitors or users of the
  Site. This Privacy Policy forms part of the Terms of Use available
  at http://www.bitcro.com/legal/tos.php.
         Some of the web search services provided herein are provided
  by Trovi Search and powered by Trovi search partners. For
  information on the web search services data collection, please visit
  http://info.trovi.com/Privacy, and the search provider's privacy
  policy, as applicable.
• CONSENT AND MODIFICATION
         By using this Site, you consent to the terms of our Privacy
  Policy and to Cro-bit Ltd.'s processing of Personal Information for
  the purposes set forth herein. If you do not agree to this Privacy
  Policy, do not use our Site and/or any of our services. Our privacy
  policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make
  sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy
  periodically.

         By visiting this Website you agree to be bound by the terms
  and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do
        not   use   or    access     our    Website.
         By mere use of the Website, you expressly consent to our use
  and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this
  Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject
  to the Terms of Use.
•  INTRODUCTION
         We respect your privacy online and recognize your need for
  appropriate protection and management of any personally
  identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with
  us.
         “Personal Information” means any information that may be
  used, either alone or in combination with other information, to
  personally identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a
  first and last name, personal profile, a home or other physical
  address, an email address or other contact information.
         Any information, video, image, data, text, documents, or
  other content posted at your direction onto a public area of the
  Site becomes publicly published content and will be available to all
  users of the Site even if such content contains Personal
  Information. Please note that if you publish your contact
  information, you may receive unsolicited messages from users and
  visitors to the Site. We encourage you to publish only information
  you are sure you want to be accessible to anyone.
         Currently, we do not require you to provide Personal
  Information in order to have access to information available on our

   Site. However, in order to provide you with certain      productsand
   services given through the Site (including the browser extensions
   services), you must create an account (“Account”) and provide us
   with your email address, a password that you will use for your
   Account and other specified information.
         Certain products and services given through the Site may
   require a fee. In order to use such services, you will be required to
   pay an applicable fee as published on the Site. We may use a third
   party payment processing company in order to collect such fee and
   you will be required to provide such third party certain personally
   identifiable information such as your name, billing address and
   credit card information. Such third party's use of such information
   will be governed by its privacy policy provided, however, that we
   use reasonable commercial efforts to limit such third party's from
   using your information for any other purpose.
3. USE OF DEMOGRAPHIC / PROFILE DATA / YOUR INFORMATION
         We use personal information to provide the services you
   request. To the extent we use your personal information to market
   to you, we will provide you the ability to opt-out of such uses. We
   use your personal information to resolve disputes; troubleshoot
   problems; help promote a safe service; collect money; measure
   consumer interest in our services, inform you about our offers,
   services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and
   protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce
   our terms and conditions; and as otherwise      described    to  you
   at the time of         collection.

  In our efforts to continually improve our product and service
  offerings, we collect and analyze demographic and profile data
  about our users' activity on our Website.
        We identify and use your IP address to help diagnose
  problems with our server, and to administer our Website. Your IP
  address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad
  demographic                                            information.
  We will occasionally ask you to complete optional online surveys.
  These surveys may ask you for contact information and
  demographic information (like zip code, age, or income level). We
  use this data to tailor your experience at our Website, providing
  you with content that we think you might be interested in and to
  display content according to your preferences.
•  THE WAY WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION
        If you submit Personal Information to us through the Site
  and/or its services, then we will use your Personal Information to
  improve our services to you, to contact you and to identify and
  authenticate your access to the Site's services that you are
  authorized to access.
        We may transfer your Personal Information within Cro-bit
  Ltd. or to Cro-bit Ltd.'s third-party authorized service providers,
  but only to provide or to offer you services through the Site and to
  personalize your experience on the services. Note that your
  information may be transferred to other jurisdictions worldwide.

      We may provide Personal Information and non-personally-
identifiable information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies,
or other third parties for the purpose of processing such
information on our behalf mainly for statistical purposes. We
require that such parties maintain the confidentiality of such
information.
      We may also use your email address to send updates, a
newsletter or news regarding our services. You may choose not to
receive email of this type by following the unsubscribe link
contained in the email provided, however, that you will not be able
to opt out of receiving notifications regarding systems updates,
service announcements or other administrative messages regarding
the site's services (including the browser extensions services).
      We     may   disclose   your Personal Information       or any
information you submitted via the Site and its services if we have
a good faith belief that disclosure of such information is helpful or
reasonably necessary to (i) comply with any applicable law,
regulation, legal process or governmental request, (ii) enforce any
agreements we may have with you including investigations of
potential violations thereof, (iii) detect, prevent, or otherwise
address fraud or security issues, (iv) protect against harm to the
rights, property or safety of Cro-bit Ltd., its users, yourself or the
public, (v) to respond to claims that any content published on the
Site or the services violates any right of a third-party, (vi) to
respond to claims that unauthorized information (e.g. phone
number, name, etc.) of a third-party has been posted on the Site

or the services, (vii) when Cro-bit Ltd. is undergoing any change in
control, including by means of merger, acquisition or purchase of
all or substantially all of the assets of Cro-bit Ltd., (viii) pursuant
to your approval, in order to supply certain services, you have
requested from Cro-bit Ltd., (ix) to let our partners, affiliates and
authorized service providers to serve you with commercials, or
(x) to collect, hold and manage your Personal Information through
a third party's cloud based services, as reasonable for business
purposes, which may be located in countries outside of your
jurisdiction.
       We, independently and/or via our authorized service
providers, may collect Anonymous Information (as defined below)
during the use of the Site and its services including when you use
any Extensions (as defined in the End User License Agreement)
downloaded from Cro-bit Ltd.'s servers. We may use Anonymous
Information or disclose it to third party service providers, to
improve our services, to enhance your experience with the Site and
its services and to offer new services of Cro-bit Ltd. from time to
time. We may also disclose Anonymous Information (with or
without compensation) to third parties, including advertisers and
partners, for purposes including, but not limited to, targeted
advertisements.
       Anonymous Information means information which does not
enable identification of an individual user, such as aggregated and
analytics information about the use of our Site and the use of the
Site's services (like any Extensions generated on Cro-bit Ltd.'s
servers) including but not limited to user's browser type, operating
system type and user's IP address.

•   COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES
         When you access or use the Site, Cro-bit Ltd. may use
   industry-wide technologies such as "cookies" and Flash (or similar
   technologies) which stores certain information on your computer
   ("Local Storage") and which will allow us to enable automatic
   activation of certain features, and make your experience on the
   Site and its services much more convenient and effortless. A
   "cookie" is a small text file that may be used, for example, to
   collect information about Site activity. Some cookies and other
   technologies may serve to recall Personal Information previously
   indicated by a Site user. The cookies used by the Site are created
   per session, does not include any information about you. Most
   browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to
   accept them, how to remove them.
         You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a
   cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser.
   However, if you block or erase cookies, or change the settings of
   Flash, your online experience may be limited.
6. WEB BEACONS
         In addition to cookies, we may employ single-pixel gifs, which
   are used to compile and collect and information in statistical form.
   The data is essential for us in order to analyze and deduce the
   pattern in the usage of our site by customers.

   These web beacons can also be attached or embedded in emails in
   order to check the status of the mail and whether they have been
   read by the recipient. This is important to check our customer
   communication mechanism.
   EMAILING through privacy@searchengage.com account
•   REFERAL
         We also request our customers to provide us with email
   addresses of their friends if they wish to use our referral system.
   This will help us in sending your friends a request on your behalf to
   join our website. You can also invite all the contacts of your email
   or other SNS accounts if you wish to, in one go. We assure you that
   we DO NOT store any username, password and other login details
   of you or any account you wish to import any contact from.
•   CHOICE
         You may choose whether or not to provide Personal
   Information to Cro-bit Ltd. The notices we will provide where Cro-
   bit Ltd. collects Personal Information on the Site should help you
   to make this choice. If you choose not to provide the Personal
   Information we request, you can still visit the Site, but you may be
   unable to access certain options, offers, and services that involve
   our interaction with you.
9. ACCESS/ACCURACY

          To the extent that you do provide us with Personal
    Information, Cro-bit Ltd. wishes to maintain accurate Personal
    Information. You may check your profile and add information,
    delete information or correct any incorrect information we have.
•    THIRD PARTY LINKS
          Cro-bit Ltd. may have certain third party links or
    advertisements. These third party hyperlinks are not affiliated to
    SearchEngage and thus, Cro-bit Ltd. does not accept any liability
    for any loss, harm or dispute arising out of the information provided
    to them by you.
          We also reserve the right to promote and publicize our
    website and related services through other websites, web pages
    and blogs. These websites may ask for and collect anonymous and
    non-personally identifiable information about you. We SHALL NOT
    be held liable for any breach or loss of information arising out of
    the scenario. We DO NOT share any personally identifiable data
    with these third party websites.
          User can always decide not to allow us to use your
    information with third party services by sending a mail at
    privacy@searchengage.com.
11. THIRD PARTY SERVICE PROVIDERS
          We retain the right to employ and use services of third parties
    to facilitate and improve our services. We may outsource some part
    of our technical or related work in order to achieve

    better efficiency and service quality. We assure you that only the
    data which is essential to smooth functioning of their part of the
    website will be provided to them. They are under contractual
    obligation not to disclose any information that we provide to them
    to any third party without prior approval from us, which in turn,
    will be approved by you.
          We may share your information with our associates, sister
    and affiliate companies and business partners. You can always
    rescue yourself from the same by sending a request at
    privacy@searchengage.com.
12. SECURITY
          We take a great care in maintaining the security of the Site,
    its services and your information and in preventing unauthorized
    access to it through industry standard technologies and internal
    procedures, including through the use of tokens and encryption
    mechanisms. However, we do not guarantee that unauthorized
    access will never occur.
13. CHILDREN’S PRIVACY
          The Site is not structured to attract nor intended for children
    under the age of 18. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect any
    Personal Information from anyone we know to be under 18 years
    of age. If you are under the age of 18, you may

    not use this Site and its services and you may not provide us with
    any Personal Information of yours.
14.  IN THE EVENT OF MERGER, SALE OR BANKRUPTCY
           In the event that Cro-bit Ltd. is acquired by or merged with
    a third party entity, we reserve the right to transfer or assign the
    information we have collected from our users as part of such
    merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. In the
    unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization,
    receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the
    application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors'
    rights generally, we may not be able to control how your Personal
    Information is treated, transferred, or used. In any of the
    circumstances described in this paragraph, the information will be
    subject to the privacy policy of the purchaser or assignee.
15. COMMITMENT
           We are committed to protecting your privacy. Protecting
    your privacy online is an evolving area, and Cro-bit Ltd.'s Sites are
    constantly evolving to meet these demands. If you have any
    comments or questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact
    us at privacy@searchengage.com. While we cannot guarantee
    privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our
    abilities as soon as possible.

16. COMPLIANCE WITH LAW
          We ensure 100% cooperation is offered to law enforcement
    agencies and legal officers in order to ensure that highest possible
    compliance with law is achieved. We reserve the right to disclose
    any information about you or which you have provided to us when
    a legally sustainable request is received by us. You will be notified
    in advance regarding the same.
17. BREACH OF PRIVACY POLICY
          Cro-bit Ltd. reserves absolute right to terminate, temporarily
    disallow or suspend any account/profile or delete certain contents
    from any profile or public domain within the ambit of this website
    if the said account or any content posted in it or by it is found to
    be against our privacy policy. The adjudication of any breach or
    dispute shall be done in accordance with TERMS OF USE.
18. EXCEPTION TO NON-DISCLOSURE AND PRIVACY OF DATA
          We assure you that we employ all the information collected
    from you, be it personally identifiable or not, for legal purposes
    and to make website experience and usage better for you. We
    reserve the right to disclose any of the information or all of it in
    following scenarios-

    •     We have reasons to believe that such disclosure is necessary
          for enforcement of law, court order, police warrant etc.
    •     When such disclosure is required for maintenance and
          protection of public health and order.
    •     When such disclosure is necessary to restore lawful rights of
          another user.
    •     When we have reasons to believe in good faith that our
          website is being utilized in order to commit a crime or civil
          wrong.
    •     When your actions on Cro-bit Ltd. are in violation of our
          privacy policy, terms of use and reviewing and posting
          guidelines or when such disclosure is essential to protect
          SearchEngage’s rights and interests.
19. YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS
          By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy
    and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do
    not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the
    posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance
    of those changes.

20.  TELL US
          We are always here to listen to your problems, feedback,
    questions    and    suggestions.    Please   write    to   us   at
    privacy@searchengage.com or give us a call at +385 97 769 39 30.
    If you are not satisfied with response from either of them, please
    contact us directly by using our mailing address at
    Cro-bit Ltd.
    Imotska 28,
    21311 Stobrec
    Croatia
    We will try our best to address your concerns.
21. YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
          California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of
    Cro-bit Ltd. who are California residents to request certain
    information regarding its disclosure of personal information to
    third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a
    request, please send an e-mail to privacy@searchengage.com.
          Please note that we are only required to respond to one
    request per customer each year.
